Peter Poole fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Peter Poole fonds
1983 - 1987
F-161
Q104814746
60 cm of textual records 74 sound recordings 6 newspapers
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION Fonds includes 84 audio cassettes digitized to 124 .wav files.
Poole, Peter
Peter Poole received a Master's degree from SFU for his thesis entitled "Organized Labour Versus the State in British Columbia." The thesis examined the British Columbia labour movement's reaction to the Social Credit government restraint program of 1983. During this period, labour organized Operation Solidarity; as well, various community groups cooperated under the umbrella of the Solidarity Coalition.
published
Full
Revised
Title of fonds based on its provenance.
The fonds consists of research material acquired by Peter Poole in the course of preparing his thesis and an earlier essay on the solidarity movement. The fonds includes taped interviews of trade union leaders, solidarity movement leaders, community activists, and legal counsel. Twenty-six of the interviews are transcribed. The fonds also includes newspapers and newsclippings, essays, publications, flyers, research notes, ephemera, a chronology of the solidarity movement, and a copy of Peter Poole's thesis.
Material was arranged by the donor.
Solidarity Coalition; Operation Solidarity; Sound recordings; Textual records; Labour; Politics
The fonds was donated to the SFU Archives in 2001 by Peter Poole.
All accessions have been processed as of March 2006. No further accruals are expected.
For other material relating to the Solidarity Coalition, see also:
* Teaching Support Staff Union fonds, series F-38-11, Operation Solidarity (1983 - 1984).
* Ellen Frank fonds, series F-82-3, Solidarity Coalition (1982 - 1984).
* Women's Bookstore collection, sub-series F-111-7-2, Feminist organizations and movements (1968 - 1985).
All files are open with no restrictions. Access to the original sound recordings is restricted for preservation reasons due to the age and fragility of the medium (audio cassette). Access is provided via digital surrogates.
Series descriptions and file and item lists are available. A biographical note written by Peter Poole is available in the appendices in the hard copy version of the finding aid maintained in the Archives Reading Room. Name access points have been provided at the item level; see the Access Points index in the hard copy version of the finding aid.
- Research files, 1983 - 1987; F-161-1; 35 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records made or received by Peter Poole in the course of preparing his thesis on the solidarity movement in British Columbia. Includes news clippings, essays, publications, flyers, research notes, ephemera, a copy of the thesis, and a chronology of the 1983 conflict between the solidarity movement and the Social Credit government of British Columbia.
  - Articles - miscellaneous, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - BCGEU material, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - B C T F, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Bills 19 and 20, 1987; F-161-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Education publications, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Essays - Solidarity related, 1983 - 1986; F-161-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Essays - Poole / Solidarity related, 1984; F-161-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Fraser Institute, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Interview Questions / Answers - point form, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Kelowna newspapers, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - NDP publications, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Okanagan College Faculty Association, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Operation Solidarity, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 161-1)
  - Operation Solidarity and the Solidarity Coalition, Kelowna BC, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Province clippings, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Socialist publications, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Solidarity Coalition, 1983 - 1984; F-161-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Solidarity Coalition Conference, Oct. 22-23, 1983, F-161-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Solidarity Times, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-21 (Newspaper box 161-6)
    - Solidarity Times, vol. 1 no. 4, November 1983; F-161-1-0-0-21-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item72.
    - Solidarity Times, vol. 1 no. 9, December 1983; F-161-1-0-0-21-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item73.
  - Solidarity Coalition Bulletin, 1984 - 1985; F-161-1-0-0-22 (Newspaper box 161-6)
    - Solidarity Coalition Bulletin, vol. 17, October 1984; F-161-1-0-0-22-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item74.
    - Solidarity Coalition Bulletin, vol. 19, February 1985; F-161-1-0-0-22-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item75.
    - Solidarity Coalition Bulletin, vol. 21, April 1985; F-161-1-0-0-22-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item76.
    - Solidarity Coalition Bulletin, vol. 24, October 1985; F-161-1-0-0-22-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item77.
  - Speeches - various, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Theory, 1983 - 1987; F-161-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Union publications, 1983 - 1987; F-161-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - The Sun clippings, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Women's publications, 1983; F-161-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 161-2)
  - Organized labour vs the State in BC - copy of Peter Poole's thesis, 1987; F-161-1-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
  - Chronology of the 1983 conflict, 1986; F-161-1-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
- Interviews and transcripts, 1984 - 1986; F-161-2; 10 cm of textual records 68 sound recordings
  Series consists of 68 interviews conducted by Peter Poole with trade union leaders, solidarity movement leaders, community activists, and legal counsel. Records include sound recordings of the interviews, lists of interview subjects, Poole's personal impressions of the tape recorded interviews and interviewees, and 26 transcripts made by students. Interviews range from one-half hour to two hours in length.
  Series was arranged by the archivist into three sub-series based on the projects for which the interviews were conducted.
  Sound recordings contained on 84 audio cassettes digitized to 124 .wav files.
  - Interviews for a previous solidarity movement essay, 1984; F-161-2-1; 1 cm of textual records 12 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 13 audio cassettes and 21 .wav files.
    During 1984, while Poole was a student at SFU, he wrote an essay on the solidarity movement, Progressive Activism and the Solidarity Movement: Towards a Radical Perspective. Interviewees were chosen from a number of left-wing activists who had been directly involved with the solidarity struggle or who had followed it closely. Sub-series includes 1 file listing interviewees and the sound recordings of the interviews.
    Items are arranged alphabetically by interviewee.
    See series 1 for a copy of the essay.
    Access to the original sounding records is restricted for preservation reasons due to the age and fragility of the medium (audio cassette). Access is provided via digital surrogates. Consult the archivist for more information.
    - Annis, Ruth: child support worker, Vancouver, 27 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3490)
      Annis, Ruth; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item1.
      - OBJ-3490_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3490_SideB.wav
    - Bostock, David: union pile driver, Vancouver, 6 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3491)
      Bostock, David; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item2.
      - OBJ-3491_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3491_SideB.wav
    - Coward, Barbara: teacher, Vancouver, 10 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3492)
      Coward, Barbara; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Barbara Coward interview starts at the 10:00 mark on Side B of OBJ-3492.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item3.
      - OBJ-3492_SideB.wav
    - Garrod, Steve: student, Vancouver, 10 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3492)
      Garrod, Steve; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Steve Garrod runs through Side A to the 10 min mark of Side B of OBJ-3492.
      - OBJ-3492_SideA.wav
    - Howard, Steven: student, Vancouver, 13 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3493)
      Steven Howard; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item4.
      - OBJ-3493_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3493_SideB.wav
    - Lyons, Phil: ex-staff training supervisor for Human Resources, Vancouver, 9 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3494)
      Lyons, Phil; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Phil Lyons interview runs through Side A to the 7:37 mark on Side B of OBJ-3494.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item5.
      - OBJ-3494_SideA.wav
    - McGuckin, Gene: pulp and paper worker, Vancouver, 8 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3494)
      McGuckin, Gene; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Gene McGuckin interview starts at the 7:37 mark of Side B of OBJ-3494.
      - OBJ-3494_SideB.wav
    - Nichol, Sandra: unemployed teacher, Vancouver, 6 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3495)
      Sandra Nichol; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3495_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3495_SideB.wav
    - Palmer, Bryan: SFU professor, Burnaby, 23 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3496)
      Palmer, Bryan; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item7.
      - OBJ-3496_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3496_SideB.wav
    - Persky, Stan: author, Capilano College professor, Vancouver, 7 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3497, Audio cassette OBJ-3498)
      Persky, Stan; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3498 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item8, F-161-item9.
      - OBJ-3497_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3497_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3498_SideA.wav
    - Sayers, Geraldine: student, ex-BCGEU member, Burnaby, 4 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3499)
      Sayers, Geraldine; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item10.
      - OBJ-3499_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3499_SideB.wav
    - Wilson, Fred: Labour Secretary for the Communist Party of Canada, 15 February 1984; F-161-2-1-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-3500)
      Wilson, Fred; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item11.
      - OBJ-3500_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3500_SideB.wav
    - List of tape recorded interviews for a previous solidarity movement essay, 1984; F-161-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
  - Interviews of Terrace/Kitimat trade unionists, 1985; F-161-2-2; 1 cm of textual records 16 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 16 audio cassettes and 15 .wav files.
    Peter Poole lived in Terrace for a number of years in the late seventies and early eighties and was especially active in the Terrace/Kitimat Labour Council). His interview subects comprised a cross-section of people from different unions and different occupations: for example, a teacher (BCTF), academic faculty from Northwest College (CUPE), a federal fisheries officer (PSAC), a library clerk (BCGEU), pulp mill workers and aluminum smelter workers (CAIMAW and CASAW), and a labourer (Rock & Tunnel Union). Records include one file listing the interviewees and the sound recordings of the interviews.
    Access to the original sound records is restricted for preservation reasons due to the age and fragility of the medium (audio cassette). Access is provided via digital surrogates. Consult the archivist for more information.
    - Corbeil, Mike: BCGEU, Kitimat, 22 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3501)
      Corbeil, Mike; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item12.
      - OBJ-3501_SideA.wav
    - Goffinet, Bob: BCTF, Kitimat, 22 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3501)
      Goffinet, Rob; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3501_SideB.wav
    - Heyman, George: BCGEU, Terrace, 21 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3505)
      Heyman, George; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item16.
      - OBJ-3505_SideB.wav
    - Kofoed, Betty: BCGEU, Terrace, 20 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3503)
      Kofoed, Betty; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3503 is blank. Interview starts at 16 minute mark of Side A.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item14.
      - OBJ-3503_SideA.wav
    - Kofoed, George: PSAC, Terrace, 20 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3503)
      Kofoed, George; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3503 is blank. Interview ends at the 16 minute mark of Side A.
      - OBJ-3503_SideA.wav
    - Lamb, Jim: CUPE, Terrace, 22 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3504)
      Lamb, Jim; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item15.
      - OBJ-3504_SideA.wav
    - Jensen, John: Carpenters' Union, Terrace, 25 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3502)
      John Jenson and Paul Johnston (F-161-2-2-0-8) are interviewed together on OBJ-3502.
      Jensen, John; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item13.
      - OBJ-3502_SideA.wav
    - Johnston, Paul: Rock and Tunnel Union, Terrace, 25 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3502)
      John Jenson (F-161-2-2-0-7) and Paul Johnston are interviewed together on OBJ-3502.
      Johnston, Paul; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3502_SideB.wav
    - Malhotra, Surinder: IWA, Terrace, 23 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3506)
      Malhotra, Surinder; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item6.
      - OBJ-3506_SideB.wav
    - MacCormick, John: Carpenters' Union, Terrace, 21 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3508)
      MacCormick, John; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item19.
      - OBJ-3508_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3508_SideB.wav
    - McKinnon, David: BCGEU, Terrace, 21 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3505)
      McKinnon, Dave; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3505_SideA.wav
    - Mueller, Claus: CASAW, Kitimat, 22 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-12; Jim Nyland and Claus Mueller were interviewed together on OBJ-3507. (Audio cassette OBJ-3507)
      Jim Nyland and Claus Mueller were interviewed together on OBJ-3705. See also F-161-2-2-0-0-14.
      Mueller, Claus; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item18.
      - OBJ-3507_SideA.wav
    - Muller, Jake: CUPE, Terrace, 23 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-3506)
      Muller, Jake; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item17.
      - OBJ-3506_SideA.wav
    - Nyland, Jim: CASAW, Kitimat, 22 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-14; Jim Nyland and Claus Mueller were interviewed together on OBJ-3507. (Audio cassette OBJ-3507)
      Jim Nyland and Claus Mueller were interviewed together on OBJ-3705. See also F-161-2-2-0-0-12
      Nyland, Jim; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3507_SideB.wav
    - Randle, Croft: TCW, Terrace, 23 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-3504)
      Randle, Croft; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3504_SideB.wav
    - Weber, Peter: CUPE, Terrace, 21 August 1985; F-161-2-2-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-3508)
      Weber, Peter; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      - OBJ-3508_SideA.wav
    - List of tape recorded interviews of Terrace / Kitimat Trade Unionists re Impression of the Solidarity Movement, 1985; F-161-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 161-3)
  - Interviews for Peter Poole's master's thesis, 1986; F-161-2-3; 8 cm of textual records 40 sound recordings; Physical description: sub-series includes 55 audio cassettes and 88 .wav files.
    Poole conducted a large group of interviews in the Lower Mainland. His subjects included labour representatives from Operation Solidarity (the trade union component of the movement), representatives from the Solidarity Coalition (the community component) and Leo McGrady, who headed the law firm that defended the unions before the Labour Relations Board and the courts.
    - Adams, Jack, 6 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-3509)
      Jack Adams was Director, British Columbia Government Employees Union (BCGEU); Executive Council member of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and a member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Adams, Jack; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item20.
      - OBJ-3509_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3509_SideB.wav
    - Alton, Monty, 15 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-3511, Audio cassette OBJ-3512)
      Monty Alton was Assistant Director in Western Canada, United Steelworkers of America; 5th Vice-President British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and a member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Alton, Monty; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3512 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item22, F-161-item23.
      - OBJ-3511_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3511_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3512_SideA.wav
    - Andstein, Cliff, 4 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-3510)
      Cliff Andstein was Director, British Columbia Government Employees Union (BCGEU); Executive Committee member of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and Negotiating Committee Chairman, BCGEU.
      Andstein, Cliff; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item21.
      - OBJ-3510_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3510_SideB.wav
    - Bartlett, Jon, 19 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-3513, Audio cassette OBJ-3514)
      John Barlett was Recording Secretary, Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition Steering Committee; and Spokesperson, Cultural Coaltion Against the Budget.
      Bartlett, Jon; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item24, F-161-item25.
      - OBJ-3513_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3513_SideB.wav
    - Blakey, Al, 1 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-3515, Audio cassette OBJ-3516)
      Al Blakey was Co-chairperson, Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition; Executive member, British Columbia Teachers' Federation; and ex-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL).
      Blakey, Al; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item26, F-161-item27.
      - OBJ-3515_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3515_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3516_SideA.wav
    - Cadman, David, 7 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-3517, Audio cassette OBJ-3518)
      David Cadman was President, Vancouver Municipal and Regional Employees Union, and public sector representative to the Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition (LMSC).
      Cadman, David; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3518 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item28, F-161-item29.
      - OBJ-3517_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3517_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3518_SideA.wav
    - Chouhan, Raj, 23 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-3519)
      Raj Chouhan was President, Canadian Farmworkers Union, and member of the Lower Mainland Solidarity Coalition (LMSC) Steering Committee.
      Raj Chouhan; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item30.
      - OBJ-3519_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3519_SideB.wav
    - Clark, Bill, 2 April 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-3520, Audio cassette OBJ-3521)
      Bill Clark was President, Telecommunication Workers' Union; 6th Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour; and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Clark, Bill; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Side B of OBJ-3521 is blank.
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item31, F-161-item32.
      - OBJ-3520_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3520_SideB.wav
      - OBJ-3521_SideA.wav
    - Dykstra, Owen, 17 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-3522)
      Owen Dykstra was President, BC division of the Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE); general Vice-President of national CUPE; Executive Council member of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.
      Dykstra, Owen; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-161-item33.
      - OBJ-3522_SideA.wav
      - OBJ-3522_SideB.wav
    - Errington, Jean, 15 July 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-3531)
      Jean Errington was Research representative for the Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE).
      Errington, Jean; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
      Interview with Jean Errington runs from 19:11 of Side B to the end of that side of OBJ-3531.
      - OBJ-3531_SideB.wav
    - Garcia, Don, 27 June 1986; F-161-2-3-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-3523)
      Don Garcia was President (Canadian area), International Longshoreman's and Warehousemen's Union; 2nd Vice-President of the British Columbia Federation of Labour (BCFL); and member of the Trade Union Solidarity Steering Committee.